

OLGA MASENG Junior Software Developer

About Me

I am a diligent Software Engineering student at CodeSpace Academy, driven by a passion for technology and a multifaceted skill set. My qualifications in End User Computing, Technical Support, and Systems Support have provided me with a solid foundation in IT, equipping me to address a wide range of digital challenges. Currently, I am on an exciting journey to become a proficient Nextjs, React & React Native Developer. I am dedicated to honing my skills in this domain and am actively working on perfecting my knowledge in React. This commitment to continuous learning reflects my determination to stay at the forefront of technology and deliver innovative solutions.



+27 81 739 4822



masengolga@gmail.com



Linked in linkedin.com/in/olga-maseng



github.com/olgamaseng



https://padlet.com/masengolga/my-<u>portfolio-hygqijhm45qgfqfn</u>

Expertise

- React
- NextJS
- JavaScript
- Microsoft Office
- Data Capturing
- CSS
- HTML
- GitHub/Git

Soft Skills

- Good communicator
- Teamwork
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability
- Creativity

Languages

- Setswana
- English
- Isizulu

Education

2023- to date

Software Development Course

Codespace Academy

2012 - 2013

System Support NQF Level 5

Bytes Technology

2011 - 2012

Technical Support NQF

level 4

Xtensive ICT Academy (Midrand)

2007 - 2008

End User Computing Level 3

Xtensive ICT Academy (Rustenburg)

2006

Grade 12

Tlhabane Technical & Commercial High School

Experience

Horizon Global 2013 - 2022

Welder(CO2, Tig, Arc and Brazing)

Trade tested in welding and became a qualified welder in 2019.

Makgetse High School

2012 - 2013

Computer Applications Technology teacher and SA-SAMS data capturer Maintaining the Computer Lab by fixing all the computers and ensuring that the computers are in good working condition before classes.

Zakheni Training and Development Centre 2009 - 2010

Peer Educator

Running awareness campaigns and going door to door ensuring that the community(Rustenburg) is aware of the issues we were tasked to make them aware of.

My References

Cherick Mashilo

Makgetse High School / Mentor 012 717 2877

Elias Bhuda

Horizon Global / Supervisor 063 117 8725

Ontiretse Motene

Bafokeng CodeLab 064 685 7101